good evening and welcome to the first
and maybe only racial draft here in New
York City folks this is for all the
marbles
what happens here will state the racial
standing of these Americans once and for
all
that's right and the crowd is here to
support their racism well Rob some of
the biggest names in sports and in
entertainment are on the line tonight
and I'm excited to see who's going to be
drafted by which race seated behind me
on the stage there are the various
representatives and believe it or not
the blacks have actually won the first
pick Wow that's the first lottery of
black person's won in a long time billet
dancing a probably still complain the
most dominant athlete in the world
his father black his mother time but it
doesn't matter anymore because now
the Asians you gotta think about it
he's been discriminated against in his
time he's had death threats and he dates
a white woman sounds like a black guy to
me ghastly why looking black girl red
paw highlights a tremendous opportunity
for me finally be part of a race have a
home been so confused by Kappa Clay's
and so many things so long fried rice
hello fried chicken
[Applause]
I always wanted to say this for shizzle
well it seems as though Tiger Woods is
happy to be black and that's a good
thing because I just received word that
he lost all his endorsements oh and
mixed tag heuer wheaties the whole
shebang-a-bang tough break it's
always all right coming up now are the
Jews
many have speculated about their picks
I'm guessing they're gonna pick Madonna
and finish off the job Kabbalah
started yes well Rob she was born and
raised Catholic then she became a
but over the last decade she has studied
the Kabbalah and she even wrote a
Kabbalah's children's book oh here come
the Jews why don't we take a look
downstairs today we the Jewish people
take Lenny Kravitz actually half-black
and half-jewish his mother was on The
Jeffersons a pivotal show in black
culture and his father a Jew was her
lawyer couldn't make that up Jewish now
unfortunately Lenny can't make it here
too except he's in Miami Beach Miami
Beach well he must have got that news
about being Jewish early all right why
don't we all take in a suture to their
case we the Latinos shoes alien go
solace
I understand that one we wanted to do
this before the white people tried to
adopt him as one of their own then okay
guess whose turn it is white people
let's see what direction they go in
Halle Berry is still available as is
Mariah Carey's crazy ass very mature
rondell
thank you all good afternoon excuse me
pardon me
Hey will you cut the malarkey okay I'm
talking there's a white man talking up
here so let's seal oh now ah thank you
damn we the white delegation are very
proud to announce our pick this year
Colin Powell old Powell is not right
he's he's not even 1/8 white he's 100%
black last night Wow I got a wonder how
the blacks are gonna be taking this one
black delegation except the white
delegations offered draft : Paul on the
condition that they also accept
Condoleezza Rice as part of the deal
[Applause]
right people everywhere
we accept got yourself a goddamn deal
black delegation requests M&M jobs a
minute Roger this what part of the park
alright well no hustling me I'm talking
to the ultimate hustler I tell you what
let's make all things fair
we keep Eminem you get OJ Simpson shot
incredible a first round absolutely
chock full of surprised unbelievable
Colin Powell and Condoleezza Rice now
officially white OJ black again what I
[Music]
think they would have picked Oprah oh
well absolutely Rob thick thighs no
felonies she definitely would have been
a great pickup ok the Chinese delegation
is up next
although they're the last they've been
waiting with a zen-like patience my
guess is yummy he's been spending a lot
of time with blacks learning slang and
shit-talking they're not careful they
might lose them the Asian delegation
chooses the RZA the GZA
[Applause]
and choosing the entire wu-tang clan
Big Boss Jokers
we've always been a fan of the Kong food
the Chinese culture is so you
always like bong bong you know yeah I
wanna remind everybody to diversify
y'all barns and Reza got announcement to
make
oh yeah Oh Dody has now changed his name
from dope new goat to the old dirty
Chinese restaurant
[Applause]
konichiwa we're going on this
incredible night our coverage ends here
but be sure to catch the rest on our
website congratulations to all the races
and konichiwa
[Applause]